[{"question":"What instrument is used to measure angles?","answers":["Protractor","Pair Of Compasses","Ruler"],"rightAns":"Protractor","qid":"1","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"Who stole Christmas in a Dr Seuss story?","answers":["Harry Potter","Grinch","Frank Sinatra"],"rightAns":"Grinch","qid":"2","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"What's the capital of Norway?","answers":["Oslo","Beanstaple","Coruscant"],"rightAns":"Oslo","qid":"3","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"Who does Mark jilt in an episode of the peep show?","answers":["Mike wazowski","Sophie","Jane"],"rightAns":"Sophie","qid":"4","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"Who scored the third goal for Wales vs. Belgium in Euro 2016?","answers":["Hal Robson-Kanu","Sam Vokes","Jar Jar Binks"],"rightAns":"Sam Vokes","qid":"5","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"What's the best quality street chocolate?","answers":["Green Triangle","Purple One","Orange Creme"],"rightAns":"Orange Creme","qid":"6","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"Who was the were-rabbit in wallace and grommit?","answers":["Feathers Mcgraw","Wallace","Wensleydale"],"rightAns":"Wallace","qid":"7","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"What is the first letter of the Greek alphabet?","answers":["Alto","Theta","Alpha"],"rightAns":"Alpha","qid":"8","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"What is a barracuda?","answers":["Dinosaur","Fish","Soap"],"rightAns":"Fish","qid":"9","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"What is the name of Shrek's wife?","answers":["Fiona","Mary","Pinocchio"],"rightAns":"Fiona","qid":"10","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"What's the fifth planet from the sun?","answers":["Mars","Jupiter","Venus"],"rightAns":"Jupiter","qid":"11","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"When did Columbus discover the Americas?","answers":["1517","1464","1492"],"rightAns":"1492","qid":"12","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"Where does the company Sony originate from?","answers":["Japan","Korea","America"],"rightAns":"Japan","qid":"13","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0}]